[
  {
    "question": "This is one of the world’s most recognizable structures. Can you save Hangman and choose the correct letters?",
    "answer": "eiffel tower"
  },
  {
    "question": "Some people claim to have none of this when it comes to dancing.",
    "answer": "rhythm"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hopefully Hangman won’t end up here, a final resting place for many.",
    "answer": "cemetery"
  },
  {
    "question": "This creature is the largest reptile in North America.",
    "answer": "alligator"
  },
  {
    "question": "Save Hangman by completing this word, meaning a deep, immeasurable space",
    "answer": "abyss"
  },
  {
    "question": "This word comes from two French words, couvrir, which means “to cover” and chef, which means “head",
    "answer": "handkerchief"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can you save Hangman by figuring out this word?",
    "answer": "instrument"
  },
  {
    "question": " William Shakespeare was perhaps the most famous one of these!",
    "answer": "playwright"
  },
  {
    "question": " If you have one of these, you can legally operate a motorized vehicle.",
    "answer": "license"
  },
  {
    "question": "This word means to accuse someone of wrongdoing!",
    "answer": "indict"
  }
]
